http://www.audon.co.uk/privacy.html

SearchAdvanced SearchProductsData Acquisition and ControlRemote IO ModulesDataloggers and Chart RecordersSerial Adapters and Protocol ConvertersIT Systems Monitor & AlarmSensors and TransmittersPLC's and Industrial ControllersHMI,
Panel PC's and LCD'sRFID Readers & ControllersPower SolutionsAccessoriesClearanceMain MenuHomeContact UsPrivacy PolicyTerms and ConditionsWEEE Directive Christmas Closure - We will be closed from 18th December 2020 until 4th January 2021 last order for despatch will be midday Friday 18th DecemberPrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy1. Introduction1.1 Audon Electronics takes the privacy of your information very seriously. This policy explains how and for what purposes we use the information collected about you either over the telephone or via www.audon.co.uk (referred to below as the "Site"). Please read this privacy policy carefully. By providing the information to us or by using the Site and any services we offer via the Site, you are agreeing to be bound by this policy in respect of the information collected about you via this Site.1.2 If you have any queries about the policy, please get in touch with us using the contact details below and we will do our best to answer your questions.2. What information we collect2.1 We will collect the following personal information from you:2.1.1 name, company name;2.1.2 email address, postal address, telephone and fax number;2.1.3 credit card information (when you wish to place an order).2.2 Although it is not compulsory to give this information, if you do not then we may not be able to provide you with the full range of services the Site has to offer.3. Use of this information3.1 We will use this information in order to:3.1.1 process orders or applications submitted by you;3.1.2 send you information about our products and services;3.1.3 verify your identity;3.1.4 carry out marketing analysis;3.1.5 to obtain your views or comments on the services we provide; and3.1.6 add your details to our mailing list.4. Information automatically collected from your computer4.1 Log Files / IP Addresses: When you visit the Site our web server automatically records your IP address. This IP address is not linked to any of your personal information. We use IP addresses to help us administer the Site and to collect demographic information for aggregation purposes.4.2 We may also gather other non-personal information (from which we cannot identify you) such as the type of your internet browser which we use to provide you with a more effective service.5. Changes to your detailsWe aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied us with, please contact us as set out below.6. SecurityWe have implemented technology and policies to safeguard your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use. All financial information provided to us is deleted when each order has been processed.7. Linking to third party websites7.1 We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links from our Site and recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.7.2 In addition, if you linked to this Site from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners or operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.8. Changes to our Privacy StatementIf we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we would notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our website notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.9. Contact usIf at any time you would like to contact us with your views about our privacy practices, or with any enquiry relating to your personal information, you can do so by sending an email to us at info@audon.co.ukSite Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions Weee Directive Site MapContact Contact Us Read Our Blog
© 2020 Audon Electronics, part of the B&S Group Ltd Companies.   Registered in England and Wales No 02573279HomeContact Us   View Basket | New Account | Sign In
